{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Turnip","incorrectAnswers":["Swede","Potato","Carrot"],"question":"From what were Jack-o-Lanterns first made?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"White","incorrectAnswers":["Maroon","Orange","Gold"],"question":"Which of these colors is included on the flag of Canada?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Woody Harrelson","incorrectAnswers":["Brad Pitt","George Clooney","Leonardo DiCaprio"],"question":"Which actor played Marty Hart on 'True Detective'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Ankara","incorrectAnswers":["Dubai","Tehran","Cairo"],"question":"Which of these cities is in Turkey?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Robert Wise","incorrectAnswers":["Steven Spielberg","Woody Allen","Martin Scorsese"],"question":"Which director directed The Sound of Music?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Sino-Tibetan","incorrectAnswers":["Austroasiatic","Indo-European","Niger–Congo"],"question":"The language 'Jin Chinese' belongs to which language family?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Elizabeth I","incorrectAnswers":["Mary I","Anne Boleyn","Victoria"],"question":"Which English queen was known as 'The Virgin Queen'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"An aftershock","incorrectAnswers":["A precursor","A temblor","A seismic wave"],"question":"What is the name for a small earthquake or tremor that occurs following a major one?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"North America","incorrectAnswers":["South America","Oceania","Europe"],"question":"The country of Saint Lucia is on which continent?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Ratt","incorrectAnswers":["Buster Poindexter","Devo","? & The Mysterians"],"question":"Who had a hit in 1984 with Round And Round?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"India","incorrectAnswers":["Ghana","Thailand","Barbados"],"question":"Masala Dosa is a dish that is most associated with which part of the world?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Hera","incorrectAnswers":["Aphrodite","Hercules","Athena"],"question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Juno?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Jarabe Tapatío","incorrectAnswers":["Salsa","Merengue","Tango"],"question":"What is the name of the national dance of Mexico?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"China","incorrectAnswers":["Spain","Brazil","Australia"],"question":"In which country did the Boxer Rebellion take place?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Indonesia","incorrectAnswers":["Solomon Islands","Federated States of Micronesia","Palau"],"question":"Which of these countries borders Papua New Guinea?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Madonna","incorrectAnswers":["Eric Clapton","Nicki Minaj","Alanis Morissette"],"question":"Which American singer released the album 'Ray of Light'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"A pack","incorrectAnswers":["A kindle","A flight","A plump"],"question":"What is the word for a group of wolves?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Steffi Graff","incorrectAnswers":["Billie Jean King","Venus Williams","Maria Sharapova"],"question":"Which player won her last tennis Grand Slam Tournament in Paris in 1999?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Eight","incorrectAnswers":["White","Seven","Green"],"question":"In German, what is the meaning of the word 'acht'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Malaysia","incorrectAnswers":["Vietnam","Singapore","Bangladesh"],"question":"Which of these countries borders Thailand?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Poison","incorrectAnswers":["The Velvet Underground","Fleetwood Mac","Blonde"],"question":"CC Deville Was A Member Of Which Band?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Blitzkrieg","incorrectAnswers":["Panzer","Sturm","Luftwaffe"],"question":"What is the German term for the 'Lightning War' that was employed by the Nazis in World War II?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Ipswich Town","incorrectAnswers":["Plymouth Argyle","Norwich City","Bristol Rovers"],"question":"Which English football team are nicknamed the Tractor Boys?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Truffle","incorrectAnswers":["Potato","Sweet Potato","Pumpkin"],"question":"Which tuber is sometimes called the 'Black Diamond'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Harper Lee","incorrectAnswers":["Kurt Vonnegut","Chester Washington","Ursula K Le Guin"],"question":"Who wrote \"To Kill A Mockingbird\"?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"France","incorrectAnswers":["Italy","Russia","Spain"],"question":"Where did the bayonet originate?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Apples","incorrectAnswers":["Bananas","Cherries","Oranges"],"question":"What fruit allegedly keeps the doctor away if you eat one per day?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Frances McDormand","incorrectAnswers":["Rachel Weisz","Frances Fisher","Salma Hayek"],"question":"Which actress has featured in films including Fargo and Transformers: Dark of the Moon?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Too Long Didn't Read","incorrectAnswers":["Top Level Domain Redirect","Tomorrow Let's Damn Remember","Trying Little Does Revolutions"],"question":"What do the letters 'TLDR' mean on internet chats?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"General Franco ","incorrectAnswers":["General Marco","General Castro","General Raul"],"question":"Who Was Head Of State Of Spain Before King Juan Carlos?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"A purr","incorrectAnswers":["A meow","A mewl","A ruff"],"question":"What is the name of the endearing cat sound that is caused by the vibration of the false vocal cords?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Happy","incorrectAnswers":["Joyful","Excited","Satisfied"],"question":"What is the one-word title of a 2014 Pharrell Williams hit?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"fossils of ancient life","incorrectAnswers":["the kidneys and their diseases, a branch of medicine","enzymes","ants"],"question":"What is Paleontology the study of?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Elton John","incorrectAnswers":["Eric Clapton","Bob Dylan","James Blunt"],"question":"Which singer-songwriter wrote the song 'Candle in the Wind'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Mozzarella","incorrectAnswers":["Gorgonzola","Feta","Camembert"],"question":"Which of these cheeses would you be most likely to find in a lasagne?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Iron Oxide","incorrectAnswers":["Magnesium sulphate heptahydrate","Calcium sulphate dihydrate","Potassium hydrogen tartrate"],"question":"What chemical has the formula Fe2O3?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Brazil","incorrectAnswers":["South Africa","Germany","Mexico"],"question":"Which country hosted the 2014 FIFA World Cup?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"A flock","incorrectAnswers":["A skulk","A down","A brood"],"question":"What is the word for a group of swifts?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Goose ","incorrectAnswers":["Sheep","Goat","Swan"],"question":"Foie Gras comes from the liver of which animal? ","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Italy","incorrectAnswers":["Ivory Coast","France","Ghana"],"question":"Where in the world would you most expect to be served Polenta?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"New Zealand","incorrectAnswers":["Dominica","Burkina Faso","Solomon Islands"],"question":"Wellington is the capital city of which country?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Isaac Asimov","incorrectAnswers":["Ursula K. Le Guin","Philip K. Dick","Stephen King"],"question":"Which author wrote 'Foundation'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Heart of Darkness","incorrectAnswers":["House of Dreams","Hamlet's Ongoing Despair","Hemmingway's Old Dogs"],"question":"Which iconic Joseph Conrad novel has the initials H.O.D.?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Libertas perfundet omnia luce","incorrectAnswers":["Et tu, Brute","Igne natura renovatur integral fredomi","Oderint dum metuant"],"question":"Which of these Latin phrases means 'Freedom will flood all things with light'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Warsaw","incorrectAnswers":["Valletta","Vilnius","Prague"],"question":"What is the capital city of Poland?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Sri Lanka","incorrectAnswers":["Pakistan","Latvia","Guatemala"],"question":"Which of these countries has red on its flag?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"The Jimi Hendrix Experience","incorrectAnswers":["Poison","The Pussycat Dolls","Three 6 Mafia"],"question":"Which psychedelic rock band released the song 'Voodoo Child'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Jerusalem","incorrectAnswers":["Bethlehem","Tel Aviv","Haifa"],"question":"Where was Solomon's Temple located?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Bette Davis","incorrectAnswers":["Audrey Hepburn","Shirley MacLaine","Vivien Leigh"],"question":"Which actress played the role of Margo Channing in All About Eve?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Czechia","incorrectAnswers":["Germany","North Macedonia","Peru"],"question":"Which of these countries has blue on its flag?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"For the good","incorrectAnswers":["Professional soldier","I am not led, I lead","Great is the power of habit"],"question":"What is the meaning of the Latin phrase 'Pro bono'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"The Lord Of The Rings","incorrectAnswers":["The Matrix","The Godfather","Jurassic Park"],"question":"Peter Jackson Is Responsible For Directing Which Famous Trilogy?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Bolivia","incorrectAnswers":["Ukraine","China","Belgium"],"question":"In which country is singani a popular drink?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Brussels","incorrectAnswers":["Luanda","Ottawa","Warsaw"],"question":"What is the capital city of Belgium?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Formicary","incorrectAnswers":["Insectabode","Tellenite","Anobide"],"question":"Where do ants live?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Eyes","incorrectAnswers":["Stinger","Wings","Lungs"],"question":"Honey Bees have hair on their ________. ","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Shaped pasta","incorrectAnswers":["Strand pasta","Tubular pasta","Soup pasta"],"question":"What type of pasta is conchiglie?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"It's A Wonderful Life","incorrectAnswers":["The Manchurian Candidate","The Pink Panther","The Birds"],"question":"Which film contains the character 'George Bailey'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Aeroflot","incorrectAnswers":["Lufthansa","TAP Air","Mosk Air"],"question":"What Is The National Airline Of Russia?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Pink Floyd","incorrectAnswers":["Wings","Rudimental","The Alan Parsons Project"],"question":"Which band includes 'Syd Barrett'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Dodoma","incorrectAnswers":["Dushanbe","N'Djamena","Juba"],"question":"What is the capital city of Tanzania?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Arnold Schwarzenegger","incorrectAnswers":["Sylvester Stallone","Jason Statham","Chuck Norris"],"question":"Which action star has featured in both Terminator and Predator?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Red Red Wine","incorrectAnswers":["Smells Like Teen Spirit","Killing Me Softly","We Can Work It Out"],"question":"Which song was originally recorded by Neil Diamond and was later covered by UB40?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"France","incorrectAnswers":["Mexico","England","Greece"],"question":"In which country would you find the Palace of Versailles?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Yankee Stadium","incorrectAnswers":["Fenway Park","Wrigley Field","Dodger Stadium"],"question":"What is the nickname of the famous ballpark that was once called 'The House that Ruth Built'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Sense and Sensibility","incorrectAnswers":["Jane Eyre","The Lady of the Camellias","David Copperfield"],"question":"Which piece of written work starts with the line 'The family of Dashwood had been long settled in Sussex.'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"The effects of radiation upon living organisms","incorrectAnswers":["Fossils of ancient life","The art of using cosmetics","Acids"],"question":"What is Actinobiology the study of?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Salam","incorrectAnswers":["Hola","Namaste","Shalom"],"question":"What is the name of the Islamic greeting for 'hello'?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Cate Blanchett","incorrectAnswers":["Natalie Portman","Kate Winslet","Helen Mirren"],"question":"Which actress has played roles including Galadriel in The Lord of the Rings and Hela in Thor: Ragnarok?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Sino-Tibetan","incorrectAnswers":["Austronesian","Koreanic","Indo-European"],"question":"The language 'Gan Chinese' belongs to which language family?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Fish","incorrectAnswers":["Cake","Cheese","Bread"],"question":"What Type Of Foodstuff Is A 'Rollmop'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Lagos","incorrectAnswers":["Casablanca","Khartoum","Luanda"],"question":"Which of these cities is in Nigeria?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Arborio","incorrectAnswers":["Pialini","Rissorio","Basmati"],"question":"Which type of rice should be used to make risotto?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"China","incorrectAnswers":["Saudi Arabia","Argentina","Cuba"],"question":"In which country would you find the Forbidden City?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Wendy's","incorrectAnswers":["McDonald's","Burger King","In-N-Out"],"question":"'Where's the beef?' Is a marketing catchphrase introduced by which fast food chain?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Lord Louis Mountbatten","incorrectAnswers":["Lord Hargreaves Fitzroy","Lord William Bowles","Lord Edison Tengay"],"question":"Who was the last British Viceroy of India?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Zambia","incorrectAnswers":["Algeria","Bangladesh","Uzbekistan"],"question":"Lusaka is the capital city of which country?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Boston","incorrectAnswers":["Paris","Memphis","Ohio"],"question":"Which city hosted a revolutionary \"Tea Party\" in 1773?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Europe","incorrectAnswers":["South America","Oceania","Asia"],"question":"The country of San Marino is on which continent?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Winnipeg","incorrectAnswers":["Toronto","Vancouver","Montreal"],"question":"What is the capital of the Canadian province of Manitoba?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Tennis","incorrectAnswers":["Football","Ice hockey","Cricket"],"question":"What sport is  famously played at Wimbledon?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Britney Spears","incorrectAnswers":["Madonna","Alanis Morissette","Nicki Minaj"],"question":"Which American singer, songwriter, dancer and actress released the studio album 'Femme Fatale'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Pheromones","incorrectAnswers":["Neurotransmitters","Hormones","Proteins"],"question":"What type of chemical calling cards are released by an animal to affect other members of its species?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Beijing","incorrectAnswers":["Shanghai","Chengdu","Hong Kong"],"question":"What is the capital city of China?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Italy","incorrectAnswers":["Croatia","Austria","Switzerland"],"question":"In Which Country Is Mount Etna?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Estonia","incorrectAnswers":["Georgia","Belarus","Canada"],"question":"Which of these countries has black on its flag?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"1928","incorrectAnswers":["1910","1937","1945"],"question":"In which year did women gain the right to vote in the UK?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Bono malum superate","incorrectAnswers":["Bona fide","Humilitas occidit superbiam","Fortiter et fideliter"],"question":"Which of these Latin phrases means 'Overcome evil with good'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"TB","incorrectAnswers":["HF","CC","AK"],"question":"What infectious lung disease is known by two letters?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"ER","incorrectAnswers":["Grey's Anatomy","House M.D.","Chicago Med"],"question":"What is the name of the NBC drama series set in County General Hospital?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Pallbearer","incorrectAnswers":["Eulogist","Composer","Bellringer"],"question":"What function did the composer Franz Schubert perform at Beethoven's funeral?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"1533","incorrectAnswers":["1633","1733","1433"],"question":"In What Year Was Queen Elizabeth The I Born?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Halle Berry","incorrectAnswers":["Judi Dench","Nicole Kidman","Sissy Spacek"],"question":"Who won the 2001 Academy Award for Best Leading Actress for playing the role of Leticia Musgrove in Monster's Ball?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Malaysia","incorrectAnswers":["Thailand","Vietnam","Indonesia"],"question":"Which country is located on the eastern border of Brunei?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"1989","incorrectAnswers":["1978","1996","1961"],"question":"When was the Tiananmen Square Massacre?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Mimosa Tree","incorrectAnswers":["Oak Tree","Maple Tree","Birch Tree"],"question":"Which type of tree is known for its fragrant, yellowish-green flowers?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Bongo","incorrectAnswers":["Lute","Ocarina","Saxophone"],"question":"Which of these is a percussion instrument?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Ben Braddock","incorrectAnswers":["Martin Jackson","Leo Quince","Harold Buck"],"question":"What Was The Name Of Dustin Hoffman's Character In The 1967 Film The Graduate?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Coypu","incorrectAnswers":["Beaver","Rat","Capybara"],"question":"Which Large Rodent Is Also Known As Nutria?","difficulty":"hard"},